<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OpenEPCIS – Privacy</title>
    <link>https://Aravinda93.github.io/tags/privacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Privacy on OpenEPCIS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://Aravinda93.github.io/tags/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy: Privacy</title>
      <link>https://Aravinda93.github.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Aravinda93.github.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;privacy-policy-of-openepcisio&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy of OpenEPCIS.io&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Updated on: 01 October 2022&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OpenEPCIS.io is part of the benelog GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG. During the usage of OpenEPCIS.io we do not utilize any of Your Personal Information to deliver or enhance the Services, nor do we send any information to other entities for analytics or any other purpose. This document explains Our policies and procedures for the collection, use, and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service. Also clarifies Your privacy rights and the manner in which the law protects You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;do-we-collect-any-data&#34;&gt;Do we collect any data?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your name, email address, phone number, or any other personally identifiable information are Not collected by Our company either directly or indirectly during the usage of the OpenEPCIS.io service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;do-we-store-any-data&#34;&gt;Do we store any data?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can contact us at Our email address &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:example@example.io&#34;&gt;example@example.io&lt;/a&gt; to find out more about Our services or offers. This is the only way we can get Your information (email-id). Your email addresses and the other details You sent in the email are momentarily retained in for responding to Your queries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;do-we-use-your-data&#34;&gt;Do we use your data?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No data is gathered by OpenEPCIS.io, and none is used for analytics or performance improvement. Additionally, none of the data or information is sent to external entities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-your-data-protection-rights&#34;&gt;What are your data protection rights?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Company would like to make sure You are fully aware of all of Your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to access&lt;/strong&gt; - You have the right to obtain copies of Your personal data from Our Company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to rectification&lt;/strong&gt; - Any information that you think is incorrect may be requested to be corrected by Our Company. Additionally, you have the right to ask Our Company to fill any information that you feel is lacking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to erasure&lt;/strong&gt; - Under certain circumstances, you have the right to ask Our Company to delete Your personal data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to restrict processing&lt;/strong&gt; - Under certain circumstances, you have the right to request that Our Company restrict the processing of Your personal data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to object to processing&lt;/strong&gt; - Under some circumstances, you have the right to object to how Our Company is using Your personal information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to data portability&lt;/strong&gt; - You have the right to ask Our Company to provide the information we have acquired directly to you or to another organization in certain circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the event that you submit a request, we have one month to answer. To exercise any of these rights, please get in touch with us at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:example@example.io&#34;&gt;example@example.io&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cookies&#34;&gt;Cookies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cookies are text files that are downloaded to Your computer and used to store information about visitor behavior and web log activity. When You visit Our website OpenEPCIS.io, we do Not use cookies or any other similar technology to automatically collect any data about You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;privacy-policies-of-other-websites&#34;&gt;Privacy policies of other websites&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are links to other websites on the Our website. You should review the privacy policies of any other websites You visit when You click on the links because Our privacy statement only applies to Our website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;changes-to-our-privacy-policy&#34;&gt;Changes to Our privacy policy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Company regularly reviews its privacy policy, and any revisions are posted on Our website. This privacy statement was most recently revised on 1 October 2022.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-contact-us&#34;&gt;How to contact us&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please do not hesitate to get in touch with us if You have any inquiries concerning the privacy policy of Our Company, the information we have on You, or how to exercise one of Your rights under data protection.
&lt;br/&gt;
Email us at: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:example@example.io&#34;&gt;example@example.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
