<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OpenEPCIS – epcis</title>
    <link>https://Aravinda93.github.io/tags/epcis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in epcis on OpenEPCIS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://Aravinda93.github.io/tags/epcis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: EPCIS</title>
      <link>https://Aravinda93.github.io/docs/introduction/epcis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Aravinda93.github.io/docs/introduction/epcis/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;epcis&#34;&gt;EPCIS:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EPCIS is an open ISO/IEC/GS1 standard that allows visibility data information to be captured and shared within an organization or between multiple organizations in the form of an event. The EPCIS event data can be used for all physical objects such as assets, products, logical units, reusable transport items, etc., or can also be used for digital objects such as music downloads, electronic books, electronic coupons, subscriptions, etc. The EPCIS standard was designed to improve cooperation between trading partners by exchanging comprehensive information on physical and digital items. The initial version of EPCIS 1.0 was released at the beginning of 2007. Later, EPCIS 1.1 and 1.2 were released in 2014 and 2016 respectively with various enhancements. The latest version, EPCIS 2.0, is published in June 2022 with a lot of significant enhancements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main objective of the EPCIS data is to provide visibility information within a specific business process. The following figure 1 describes how EPCIS data may be generated within a simple business process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./Fig1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Figure 1: Generation of EPCIS events in a simple business process.&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Above figure depicts a simplified business process in which a manufacturer produces an item, which is then packed and shipped to the Retailer DC (Distribution Center). The item is received by Retailer DC, who then sends it to the appropriate Retail Store. The item is received by the retail store and moved to a sales area where a consumer can purchase it. The simplified flow of goods can consist of the following critical tracking events: packing, shipping, receiving the items, etc. At every step within these business processes, an EPCIS event is created. This EPCIS event provides information on what exactly was occurring to the items at that particular step. The entirety of all these EPCIS events provides a complete picture of the whole business process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EPCIS events consist of context information comprising the five different dimensions What, When, Where, Why, and How. Each of these dimensions consists of multiple fields that make up the event information. Each dimension is independent of one another and not mandatory to include all dimensions/fields of dimensions in the EPCIS event. For example, the following pieces of information are produced for four dimensions when a product is shipped from the manufacturer to retail DC in the V2 business process mentioned above:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&lt;/strong&gt;: It contains what items or containers were sent to DC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: It contains the date-time information when the items were shipped, along with the respective time zone offset information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: It contains information about the location from where the shipment was sent. Also, where the items are expected to be after the event has occurred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why&lt;/strong&gt;: It contains the business context of the information. For example, the business step in this particular event is shipping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;areas-of-application-for-epcis&#34;&gt;Areas of application for EPCIS:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EPCIS can stitch together individual events that have occurred over time in a particular supply chain within an organization or across multiple organizations. Hence, EPCIS provides many applications, such as:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracking&lt;/strong&gt;: An organization can find exactly where the objects are present within the supply chain using the most recent EPCIS event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracing&lt;/strong&gt;: An organization can track the objects to their origin using all EPCIS events associated with the particular object.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analysing&lt;/strong&gt;: All the EPCIS events collected over a particular time can be interpreted in a specific business context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automation&lt;/strong&gt;: EPCIS events can trigger various other business processes in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Verification&lt;/strong&gt;: Comparison of the real-time status of the object using the current EPCIS event and the anticipated state of the object.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefits-of-epcis&#34;&gt;Benefits of EPCIS:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EPCIS can be used in various industries such as automotive, healthcare, food services, transport, retail, etc. It provides many benefits to organizations and customers, depending on the type of industry sector. Following are some most common beneficial aspects of the EPCIS standard in various industry sectors:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Identify the origin of the object to support anti-counterfeit measures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Identify a chain of custody for an object along with date and time information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Validation of digital coupons in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Recognise the freshness of the product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Provide notification on various attributes such as location, timing, status, quantity, or quality of the product in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Ensure that items reach the consumers at the right location and time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Increase consumer protection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;openepcis&#34;&gt;OpenEPCIS:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;benelog GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG is an organization located in Kerpen, Germany that focuses on development of software and system architecture. The developed software and applications operate effectively and efficiently in the fields of big data processing, complex, scalable, cloud-based environments. benelog GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG designed and developed OpenEPCIS implementation based on the EPCIS standard. We assist businesses in seamlessly and successfully integrating the EPCIS standard into their supply chain management systems by using OpenEPCIS. We also contributed to the standardization of EPCIS 2.0 as a core member of the GS1 group. We have created several open source tools and projects associated with EPCIS standards as part of our contribution to the EPCIS community, which any entity can utilize for their use (Note: more on the tools and projects discussed later in this documentation). Email us at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:example@example.io&#34;&gt;example@example.io&lt;/a&gt; if you would like to contact us with any questions or to collaborate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;references&#34;&gt;References:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read more about EPCIS: &lt;a href=&#34;https://confluence.company-group.com/display/OEPCISDOC/EPCIS+in+a+Nutshell&#34;&gt;https://confluence.company-group.com/display/OEPCISDOC/EPCIS+in+a+Nutshell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;
    img {
        width: 600px;
        display: block;
        margin: 0 auto
    }
&lt;/style&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Introduction</title>
      <link>https://Aravinda93.github.io/docs/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Aravinda93.github.io/docs/introduction/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The supply chain system is made up of several organizations, events, people, and tools that are participating in delivering services or goods to customers. All physical and digital products progress through some form of supply chain activities before reaching the possession of customers. The accessibility and visibility of the product data throughout its life cycle in the supply chain is the primary concern for the organization as it needs to track the products in real-time and if required convey the relevant information to customers or other organizations. If each organization or entity involved in the supply chain system uses its own schema or model to keep track of the items then it is very difficult to track the products end-to-end and makes it hard for an organization to communicate with other organizations and share the data. To address this issue, there was a need for a standard that could be implemented by all businesses within their supply chain system so as to enable tracking, tracing, and monitoring of goods at every step of the supply chain. Hence, GS1 introduced the global standard known as EPCIS (Electronic Product Code Information Services).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gs1-global-standard-one&#34;&gt;GS1 (Global Standard One):&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The GS1 is a non-profit organization that develops and maintains standards for the identification, capture, and sharing of information. GS1 was established in April 1974 and is based in Brussels, Belgium. GS1 standards are being used by over 2 million businesses throughout the world. In 1974, GS1 standardized the EAN/UPC (European Article Number/Universal Product Code) barcode, which is still used and printed on a wide range of items today. GS1 operates in various industries like retail, healthcare, logistics, food service, technical industries, etc. GS1 has developed a standard for creating and sharing visibility data within and across multiple organizations known as EPCIS (Electronic Product Code Information Services). Using the standards designed by GS1 various trading partners such as customers, suppliers, distributors, logistic service providers, retailers, etc. can use a common language for communication in their supply chain. The main goal of GS1 standards is to enhance the physical and digital supply chain performance, safety, security, and accessibility. GS1 has around 115 member organizations in various countries across the globe.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Documentation</title>
      <link>https://Aravinda93.github.io/docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Aravinda93.github.io/docs/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This section provides an introduction to EPCIS, OpenEPCIS, related projects and several other OpenEPCIS-related topics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://Aravinda93.github.io/docs/introduction/&#34;&gt;EPCIS&lt;/a&gt; section which provides overview of the EPCIS.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy: Privacy</title>
      <link>https://Aravinda93.github.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Aravinda93.github.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;privacy-policy-of-openepcisio&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy of OpenEPCIS.io&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Updated on: 01 October 2022&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OpenEPCIS.io is part of the benelog GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG. During the usage of OpenEPCIS.io we do not utilize any of Your Personal Information to deliver or enhance the Services, nor do we send any information to other entities for analytics or any other purpose. This document explains Our policies and procedures for the collection, use, and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service. Also clarifies Your privacy rights and the manner in which the law protects You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;do-we-collect-any-data&#34;&gt;Do we collect any data?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your name, email address, phone number, or any other personally identifiable information are Not collected by Our company either directly or indirectly during the usage of the OpenEPCIS.io service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;do-we-store-any-data&#34;&gt;Do we store any data?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can contact us at Our email address &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:example@example.io&#34;&gt;example@example.io&lt;/a&gt; to find out more about Our services or offers. This is the only way we can get Your information (email-id). Your email addresses and the other details You sent in the email are momentarily retained in for responding to Your queries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;do-we-use-your-data&#34;&gt;Do we use your data?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No data is gathered by OpenEPCIS.io, and none is used for analytics or performance improvement. Additionally, none of the data or information is sent to external entities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-your-data-protection-rights&#34;&gt;What are your data protection rights?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Company would like to make sure You are fully aware of all of Your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to access&lt;/strong&gt; - You have the right to obtain copies of Your personal data from Our Company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to rectification&lt;/strong&gt; - Any information that you think is incorrect may be requested to be corrected by Our Company. Additionally, you have the right to ask Our Company to fill any information that you feel is lacking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to erasure&lt;/strong&gt; - Under certain circumstances, you have the right to ask Our Company to delete Your personal data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to restrict processing&lt;/strong&gt; - Under certain circumstances, you have the right to request that Our Company restrict the processing of Your personal data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to object to processing&lt;/strong&gt; - Under some circumstances, you have the right to object to how Our Company is using Your personal information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The right to data portability&lt;/strong&gt; - You have the right to ask Our Company to provide the information we have acquired directly to you or to another organization in certain circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the event that you submit a request, we have one month to answer. To exercise any of these rights, please get in touch with us at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:example@example.io&#34;&gt;example@example.io&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cookies&#34;&gt;Cookies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cookies are text files that are downloaded to Your computer and used to store information about visitor behavior and web log activity. When You visit Our website OpenEPCIS.io, we do Not use cookies or any other similar technology to automatically collect any data about You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;privacy-policies-of-other-websites&#34;&gt;Privacy policies of other websites&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are links to other websites on the Our website. You should review the privacy policies of any other websites You visit when You click on the links because Our privacy statement only applies to Our website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;changes-to-our-privacy-policy&#34;&gt;Changes to Our privacy policy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Company regularly reviews its privacy policy, and any revisions are posted on Our website. This privacy statement was most recently revised on 1 October 2022.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-contact-us&#34;&gt;How to contact us&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please do not hesitate to get in touch with us if You have any inquiries concerning the privacy policy of Our Company, the information we have on You, or how to exercise one of Your rights under data protection.
&lt;br/&gt;
Email us at: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:example@example.io&#34;&gt;example@example.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imprint: Imprint</title>
      <link>https://Aravinda93.github.io/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Aravinda93.github.io/imprint/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;imprint&#34;&gt;Imprint&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;site-operator-isd--5-tmg&#34;&gt;Site Operator i.S.d. § 5 TMG&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Written by &lt;a href=&#34;example@example.io&#34;&gt;OpenEPCIS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Bahnhofstrasse 11 &lt;br/&gt;
50169 Kerpen  &lt;br/&gt;
Germany  &lt;br/&gt;
Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info@example.com&#34;&gt;info@example.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;commercial-register&#34;&gt;Commercial Register&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Register court: District Court of Cologne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Register number: HRA 30459&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;managing-director&#34;&gt;Managing Director&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas Hirsch&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;sales-tax-identification-number-according-to--27-a-sales-tax-law&#34;&gt;Sales tax identification number according to § 27 a sales tax law&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DE236709438&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;responsible-for-content-according-to--55-abs-2-rstv&#34;&gt;Responsible for content according to § 55 Abs. 2 RStV&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas Hirsch (address as above)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;copyright-and-photo-credits&#34;&gt;Copyright and Photo Credits&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The content and works on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.openepcis.io&#34;&gt;www.openepcis.io&lt;/a&gt; are subject to German copyright law. The duplication, editing, distribution and any kind of exploitation outside the limits of copyright require the written consent of the respective author or creator. Photographs used may be marked with photo credits or listed below if they were not taken by the author. The use of photographs on third-party sites is only possible within the framework of the respective license of the author.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Image sources: @unsplash &lt;a href=&#34;https://unsplash.com&#34;&gt;https://unsplash.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;disclaimer&#34;&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have compiled and checked the listed content with great care. However, we do not assume any liability for the completeness or topicality. We are not responsible for external content to which we refer.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
